I like!
Hallo! Ste! This time I'll be talking with Akane Haga from Morning Musume。 24 and Rikako Sasaki from Angerme!
This time, we're going to introduce you to the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
Please, Akane, it's a day early, but happy 22nd birthday to you!
Thank you very much and Happy Birthday! The same age! Yes, the same age! Rikago-chan turned 23 in May.
But that means we turned 22 about 10 months ago!
I feel like she's my sister even though we're the same age.
That's a lie! I'm not lying!
I have a certain goal for my 22nd year.
I'm going to be a graceful person.
I see.
I wonder what that means.
I'm hoping to become an elegant person with mature gestures.
I want to be elegant.
Not crass.
Not in a crass way, but in a graceful, relaxed way.
We are such a person...
The difference in the number of trainees is about half a year.
But if I count them, they've been with us for about 10 years, more than 10 years.
That's a long time.
It's almost as if we met when we were babies.
It's March, and the spring tour is about to start. will start on March 16.
This will be the first tour under the new organization after Mizuki Fukumura's graduation last year, and with a new leader.
We are also very excited and nervous about how the tour will turn out, but we believe it will be a wonderful tour, so we hope you will come and enjoy it!
And we, Angerme, too!
Angerme Concert Tour 2024 Spring
Secret Secret will start on April 6!
After this tour, I will be graduating.
This will be my last tour.
I think it's time for me to call it my last tour.
I think that the time has come for me to go on my last tour, but I don't really feel it yet.
I'm wondering when I'll be able to feel the graduation.
I really hope I can be happy with many people on this last tour.
I hope I can be happy with many people on this last tour.
Now then, please take a look at this video.
I am the heroine of this era!
I can't lose!
Mr. Spee Oh yeahOh yeahOh yeah
Oh yeah
No more no more
A young man is born
And beyond that I say
Our present
I don't know
I can't divide
Wherever the chains are
I'd chew through those chains.
I thought you had a forehead.
I think I might have dyed it.
You're a quiet one, sister.
I know what's in your heart.
Me, me, me, me, me.
This is the future of maidens.
No, the times, they are perfect.
I'm ready.
What are you sighing for?
Why do you yearn?
At the bottom of a night of tears
I'm unraveling my nails
Hey, what about you?
Look what I made you lose
It's my style
Cause I'm watching my dreams
It hurts too
Trust me.
Try to survive
A little sound steals your heart
A little briefcase fires up in the modern age
Let's go... from the back of the house... and sing our song to the top of our lungs
I wish I could be, I wish I could be
I want to be the one you don't know
Why do you live for?
why do you long to be
I want to make a name for myself now
I want you to hold on to your name, and give me the Eva code, the answer
What's wrong with Japan today?
It's my time
It's not enough, it's just the beginning
You too, love yourself for who you really are
Love.
Even from me
Just from me
I've been doing this for years.
Ahh
♪ I've got this, I've got that, I've got that, I've got the power of the roulette game
♪ I'll show you what I'm made of
Don't let go of my hand
♪ Don't let go, don't let go, go!
♪ One sparkle, one twinkle and it's all yours
It's up to you, it's up to me, it's up to me
Blue Game Power
Sometimes I'll show you what I'm made of
With you, I won't flap my wings
Now, Japan is individual
Countdown
Stand up with one hand, it's just the beginning
Cha-cha-cha!
I don't love you, you don't love her, and I don't love myself.
I kept my voice down.
I hid my heart from you.
I just want you to know that I love you... and I love you.
Countdown!
Drink some cocoa and stay warm!
This is Akemi Haga of Morning Musume 24 and Rikako Sasaki of Angerme.
and Rikako Sasaki of Angerme.
We'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
So let's answer them without thinking too much.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Okay, I'll read out the questions.
What's on your mind for fashion this spring?
Hats.
You joined the Halo Pro trainees in March 2013.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you look back over the past 11 years?
The announcement of my debut.
What do you always keep in mind when expressing yourself?
Facial expression
What was the first word you spoke to me when you were a trainee?
8 Yakata Genki Desuka Lastly, Rikako who has announced her graduation, what do you want to accomplish in your remaining time as a member of Fangurum?
What is it that you want to accomplish in the rest of your time as Fangurume?
Looking back on the past 11 years, the most memorable moment for me was...
The most impressive moment for me looking back on the past 11 years was the time of our debut, wasn't it?
Well, there's been nothing but impressive things in the past 11 years.
Yes, yes...
I can't talk about them all here.
Yes.
So many things happened.
But when I was a trainee...
I mean, when I was a trainee, the nearest goal was to make my debut.
So, after all of that preparation, I was able to make my debut one rank higher,
I was very impressed by the fact that my debut was another step up in my mind,
It was also impressive to me that my debut was with Angerme and S/mileage,
I think it was a very big event for me because it made me who I am today,
So, I think it was a big event for me.
And then there was the look on my face when they announced it.
I knew I had a great reaction when I saw my face.
Yes, it was a surprise, wasn't it? So that was part of it.
I thought it was really memorable and nice, so I had a conversation with him.
Next, the first words you spoke to me when I was a trainee at Halo Pro.
I was most curious, too.
Hey, how are you?
I'm not.
Here I go.
You like Kudo, right? We're the same.
I'm with you. What's with you? You like Egg, don't you?
No, wait, I'm about to say something embarrassing like "Hello from the Land of the Navel" or "Jeck Video Shooting".
I remember the first time we met on the day of the video shoot.
I thought it was a very formal world, so I thought, "Oh, my God!
I thought it was a very stiff world, so I was surprised to see how frank some of my seniors were.
I felt my nerves were loosened there.
So it was a really nice thing to hear.
It was so warm. Thank you for the warmth.
Thank you very much.
Akane's question is after the vtr. Ste. meme
me
Me, me, me.
I'm going to ask Akane-chan a question, and she will turn 22 years old in a few hours.
What do you think you are doing at the moment you turn 22?
Holding my dog in my arms.
Jumping.
Over the New Year?
Here we go!
Today is the anniversary of round-the-world trip
Which country would you like to visit?
France
After 9 months since joining the 17th term, what has been your most memorable experience as a teacher/educator?
The most memorable moment, or rather the most recent, was when I pulled up my socks. I did.
That's nice.
And now for the next question.
What is your favorite thing about me?
I like your friendliness and warmth.
I also like your face.
Well, that's nice.
Okay, next question.
This September marks the 10th anniversary of my joining Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
What would you like to update before then?
I guess it's the way I look at you.
Oh, the way you look at me.
Yes, I do.
I mean...
Yes, sir.
Oh!
That's good.
Can I just explain the socks before you ask me a few questions? Of course, yes! Oh! That's great!
Can I just explain the socks before you ask?
Well, at this year's HaloCon, when I was touring the various regions...
You know, there are socks for sale in many places.
The characters on those socks looked exactly like the two of you.
One of them is a character eating a ham and ham with a souvenir from the local area.
This one looks just like Haruka Inoue.
The other one looks like Aoko, the girl I dreamed up, when she gives a salute and makes a sharp face.
The difference between that fluffy and crisp look...
I thought it was perfect for the flexible Kitty.
I had already brought it to the cashier before I knew it.
I thought, "I want to give this to her.
The fluffy pishi was so cute and impressive that I bought it.
I see. Well, let me ask you one more question.
This September is the 10th anniversary of Morning Musume。 What do you want to update by then?
I said, "The way I look at things.
The eye line, yes. Of course, I want to look at the audience, but I also want to look at the audience when I sing,
I think it's the way I look at the audience when I sing, or when I dance,
My left hand? I have a habit of looking to the left or to the upper part of the stage when I dance.
When I look at the video, I feel like I have a certain line of sight.
I'm hoping to create a new line of sight.
I hope to create a new perspective.
That's good.
Looking up and down
Right eye
Or even diagonally.
I'd like to look at it from an angle.
That's right.
I'd like to improve the way I use my eyes.
I wish I could improve more and more, but I can't.
We'll continue after this.
Hello Kitchen, this time we have a member here with us. I'm Hana Goto.
I'm Hana Goto.
I'm Angerme.
Please say a few words.
I've never cooked before, but I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
So, what would you like to cook this time?
Today we're making meat pies.
Oh! Meat pie!
I've never had a meat pie.
You've never had a meat pie? I don't think so.
I have.
Not so much.
You don't get a chance to eat it.
You can't find it in stores.
I'm looking forward to it.
Do you cook, Hana-chan?
I don't cook at all, so I'd like to learn how to cook and cook at home.
I see. I'm sure you have a lot of questions, so let's ask your teacher and let's get cooking.
Sensei, what should I start with first, because first I need to make the filling for the meat pie.
Chop up the onions.
I don't know if this is the first difficulty, or maybe this is the last.
Oh, no, no, no!
Hana-chan, can you use a knife? I'm sure I can use it.
Hanana, can you use a knife?
It should work!
Oh, I should be able to use it!
Did you remember how to chop? I saw it in a home economics textbook.
Chopped, tiny, isn't it?
Chopped and tiny.
Oh, tiny.
That's good, isn't it?
Just like you did before. Just start at the top and work your way down.
Do you like cooking?
I think so.
I don't cook at all.
You said you've never done much.
It went surprisingly smoothly.
Better than I expected.
What did you think?
I can't do it at all.
I don't know what to do.
I thought I'd end up screaming the whole time.
It's all right, isn't it?
You're good!
Okay, about 30 onions.
A little at a time.
Please.
I'll give you 30 in one shot.
She's a numbers girl.
I'll give it a shot.
That's close.
So close.
One down.
Shall we take one off?
Okay, down one.
Okay.
You're going to cook it.
Will it hurt my eyes if I heat it up?
No.
But it didn't hurt your eyes?
Yes, I did.
So it's a good cut.
Yay!
And maybe it's because I'm wearing contact lenses.
No, no, no, it's okay. Maybe it's because I'm wearing contacts because I don't want the doctor or anyone else to see me. No, no, it's okay. I don't want the doctor or anyone else to see me.
I've never heard of a contact guarding you. Sometimes.
You were fine.
Yes, I was fine.
I mean, with this amount, I don't even need another minute.
Yes, about 30 seconds in the microwave for putty.
Please put this one in here.
Are you saying "Bong"?
I'm saying "bong.
Put the salt in here.
Here.
Here, Miyagi-like.
Only salt for the ground meat.
Hana-chan is going to get addicted to this... Isn't this a little dry?
I wondered what you just asked for.
You startled me.
It was so sudden.
I wanted music.
What was it?
"Para-para," he said, "it's going to stand up.
"Para para para" is no longer "para para"!
Nebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebanne!
Nebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebannebanneban
Wow, you can really sing... and it comes right out of your mouth... with a quick ad-lib... all of it... like Ms. Deva's aura and numbers and combat power... I don't know about combat power, but...
I don't know what his battle power is, but what do you see?
I don't know what a six looks like or what color it is or anything like that.
I don't know what a six looks like, or what color, or anything like that, but before we started filming, she said to me.
He said that to me.
But I've heard of people who can really see that kind of aura,
I'm told this every time by people who help me with my outfits and other things.
Six?
So for a long time, I've been very interested in the number 6,
I put 6 in the number when I decide on a number,
So when Hana-chan said something like 6, I thought, "Really? I thought, "Really?
Wow! I was quite surprised, but the teacher wanted to know about it.
Well, even this is difficult, isn't it? I guess it is.
It's kind of difficult. But first of all, it's not the eyes, it's the letters.
Not numbers?
There are numbers, too.
There are letters, too.
It's the person's image.
I don't know, white is something else.
White?
White is something else.
You mean white looks like something else?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
What is it, like an aura? You can see colors?
Some people can see colors, some people can't.
So you think it's green. Is it green?
I think so, but I don't really know.
I don't know. But can I ask you something?
I'll tell you. My first name is Takahiro.
I know my name, but I don't know it.
I don't know. And you said "Ta" from the top.
That's right. That's why I'm nervous.
You're right, I did have goosebumps.
Wow, you said the color, didn't you? You're right. I was thrilled. Indeed. Wow, I got a little goosebumps.
The color is this gray mixed with a little bit of blue, not this dark, but it's like a blue-gray, like the color of the teacher's phone.
That's amazing.
It's amazing.
I see.
What do you think?
I think it's this color.
It looks grayish.
That's true, but it's a little...
A little dark on gray.
Dark, indeed.
The backpack is this color, too.
A little more blue.
Maybe there's something in it.
I'm scared.
The backpack is this color, too.
Oh, no... Oh, no...
It's all right now.
After this...
I'm going to put in a lot of stuff.
He'll talk the whole time.
You can say it.
One more time.
Here it comes.
And then...
I'll make two today.
Please cut them in half.
Cut it in half.
That's fine.
Here.
Okay, that's it.
Wash it.
Well, that's all for now.
Well done, you've done a great job.
Next time
Let's work hard!
Let's work hard to complete the project!
Enjoy!
Wow, it looks like a fish!
Please give me a minute.
Wow! There's so much juice coming out of the meat!
I want to talk to you about something I'm addicted to... something I ate recently, but I know it's called chimney bread and there wasn't any... it's called chimney bread.
It was a hot topic last year and I didn't know about it at all.
I didn't know about it at all, but when you told me about it, I looked it up and found out that it's like this.
It's like a rusk, but it's a tube, and the bread is wrapped around a stick, and it comes in all kinds of flavors.
It comes in all kinds of flavors.
Wow.
It was crispy, crunchy, fluffy, delicious-looking bread.
I had the cinnamon one.
I had the cinnamon one, and I thought it was delicious.
The chimney buns were originally a Hungarian food, but they became popular in Korea.
I see that it landed in Japan, and there is a store in Shin-Okubo, and I went to Shin-Okubo.
I'm not really addicted to it, but the most delicious thing I've eaten recently is Entsuppan in Shin-Okubo.
I'm also a big fan of Korean food,
It's delicious.
And maybe this winter, I started to like spicy food more,
Oh, really?
Yes. I used to be a strong spicy food lover, but recently I've become even stronger,
Wow.
You know, I really like Korean food.
What do you like best? I like mandu.
I like mandu, which is like dumplings.
I also like tteokbokki. It's a little bit like that.
I'll say it a little more than the real thing.
That's right.
I like a lot of things. I know a lot more than in Korea.
Are you talking about the real thing?
No, I'm not.
I am not familiar with Korea, but I really love it, and I also like Korean dramas,
I love Korean dramas, too, so watching them makes me want to eat.
Yes, that's right. I also like Korean dramas, so watching them makes me want to eat.
The other day, while watching a Korean drama, I ordered delivery.
I had chicken, and I was eating chicken.
It was like I went to that world.
Food is great, isn't it?
It's amazing that you can eat spicy food.
I can't eat it.
You can't eat it?
I can't eat kimchi.
But it's okay if you can't eat kimchi.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
There are a lot of people in Angerme who can't eat kimchi.
That's right.
Yeah, and I can't even eat spicy food anymore.
huh?
I wonder how far they'll go to talk about it.
They're all members.
I see.
So you're still in? The ones who can still make it.
You're the one who's ready.
That feels good... and I'm gonna keep eating.
Let's eat.
Hello! Ste.
Morning Musume。 24's Akemi Haga and Rikako Sasaki of Angerme
Rikako Sasaki of Angerme will be presenting "Halo! Ste.
Project 2024 Winter 3 of us ended at the end of last month. Project 2024 Winter 3 of us ended at the end of last month!
Thank you for your hard work, Machaka!
This time, I've written down some of the memorable moments from the tour in this sketchbook, and I'd like to share them with you.
Okay, let's go!
Okay, I'll start by explaining that I'm team A this time.
I was a member of Team A, which consisted of Chibaki Factory, Beyoncé, and the original team.
Chibaki Factory, Beyon and the original team.
The song we performed as a shuffle was "Say Hello" by Halo Pro trainees.
This is "Say Hello" by Halo Pro Trainees.
We also performed this song on the album "Let's Say Hello".
We were the original members, but we didn't have the chance to work together for 10 years or so.
We didn't have a chance to work together for about 10 years, and now we've done it, and you must be really jealous.
If it hurts, I've never performed on this original album, but Say Hello and Idol is a Robot, from the Showa Era.
I've never performed these two songs before, but now that they're finally done, I'm really happy.
I'm kind of happy.
Yes! I wanted Kako-chan to do it.
I was able to participate only in that part.
Suddenly you joined TVA!
Suddenly Maria and Maria Makino dropped by together.
It was Maria's first time at Say Hello.
When we were rehearsing, the director told us
He said, "I think everyone is used to singing this song.
We're doing it for the first time with Red and Maria.
We've never done it before.
I said, "It's the first time for me and Maria to sing this song.
So I said, "Yes, this is the song I'm going to sing.
But I'm really happy that we did it.
I'm very happy too. Thank you very much.
And I'm in the...
I'm in the dance club.
Oh, wow.
Yes, this is the dance club.
Well, A and B...
I think there are two dance clubs.
The A and B dance clubs have different choreography.
But when they rehearse, they do it together.
So when they saw the A team dancing
And then we danced the next dance, and so on, and so on.
The A team had so much power, and they were really cool.
They were really cool.
I've always loved dancing.
But there are a lot of kids like that in the dance club.
So I really like this space.
But I don't know...
I don't know what it is, but there's
I don't mean that we are rivals.
It's not like we're rivals, but when we can show something better than our own team, I guess,
I was rehearsing with a feeling of "Let's do it, too!
During the rehearsals, Sakura-chan from JuiceJuice would watch us every time we rehearsed at the venue.
I was so happy that she was watching us every time,
Then, one day, Ms. Sasaki approached me,
I really like your dance,
She said, "Wow, you're so cute!
And then another day, she told me how great I was today. Even though it was a rehearsal.
And another day, she told me that Sasaki-san was amazing today, too, even though it was a rehearsal. I was like, "How do you do that?
How do you lower the center of gravity? How do you lower your center of gravity?
I was really happy to hear that. I was so happy to hear that, and on the other day, I heard that I cried today.
I have been really supported by Sakura-chan in this Team B dance club.
I'm saying this for the first time here.
She is one of the members who really motivated me, so I wanted to take this opportunity to say thank you.
I think I'll be able to show you many cool dances, so thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Sta.
Well, you know, 3 of us, I heard that this was the last winter tour for me.
I'm going to miss you so much!
But I guess a Hello Project concert is...
But a Hello Project concert was originally created with all the groups...
But... there was a sense of sadness that I couldn't experience it at the very end... but also a sense of joy that it's back.
I'm happy to see the return of the form. I have so many feelings.
I'm feeling sad that I didn't get to experience it at the very end, and happy that it's back to the way it was.
I've been thinking about it a lot at Juice Juice Tea Room Angerme, and it's the same for everyone who's on stage.
I love the personalities of each and every one of you.
It doesn't matter if they're my seniors or juniors or whatever.
I think that this is an environment where each and every one of you is a wonderful person.
I was really looking forward to meeting you all, and I was really happy when you asked me to take a picture with you, and I was really happy when you said that.
It was really fun to be able to share time with everyone like this.
I really enjoyed being able to share time with everyone like this.
Like, "I like this part..." or "Your hair looks so cute today...".
or "Your hair looks really cute today.
or "Let's make them the same color!
Even when they're in the catering line, they'll tell you how delicious it was.
There are juniors who talk to me a lot about even the smallest things.
It warmed my heart every day.
I almost cried when I saw their performances.
I always thought they were amazing.
I always thought that Hello Project was amazing, and it was always the most powerful thing I've ever seen, and I always thought that everyone was amazing.
I always thought that everyone was amazing.
Hello Project is amazing!
PROJECT is always the most powerful thing I've ever seen.
PROJECT is the best!
Thank you for your continued support!
POP! MUSIC! BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM
BOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM
BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM
BOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM
BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM BOOM
Even though I heard it for the first time
I miss love so much
Pop!
The melody is kind of sad
Whatever it is, it's going around in my head
It's...
Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! Tail color's right, that's because if you notice a little bit of it, it makes sense if it's useless
It's just analog chords from the old days
Our screams, we have to hit it
I'm just trying to grab you and make a big sound
I was stepping somewhere
We've mastered the internet, we've mastered email
We're the opposite, we're more chattering
we've lost our phones and that's it
I'm standing there in despair
Churuchuru
Penu penu
I paint your hair with hair paint
I'll stir it all up
I'll forget you in time
But I hope to see you again someday
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop music.
I've never been here before, but I feel strangely nostalgic
Pop, pop, pop, pop music
I can't help but feel sad about the catchy melody
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop music
I'm pretending I'm not interested, but I'm a little curious about it. I mean, frankly, I'm in the mood.
What are you pretending to be at the top, BeeAh-Ju-Ju-S?
Ah-Ju-Ju-S.
Pop!
I've never been here before, but I feel strangely nostalgic.
Pop! Pop! Pop! Music!
Pop!
Doraemon's gaze, his point of view, his body is moving
And then...
Pop!
I mean, I'll ask you one more time
I can't wait
Pop, Pop, Pop, Pop, Pop, Music!
Yeah, it's our first day back
Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! Music!
Pop! Pop! Pop! Music!
Whatever it is, it's natural
My body is moving.
I mean, notice the last thing I said.
I mean, notice at the end when I say this crazy nabilin'... in this song.
I'm gonna get a good night's sleep this time.
What do you want?
Akane Hanegawa of Morning Musume 24 and
and Rikako Sasaki of Angerme.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Yes, Morning Musume。24 Concert Tour Spring
More Morning Musume。 will start on March 16th!
This will be the first tour since the new tour started.
We will all do our best!
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
And Angerme is going to start
Angerme Concert Tour 2024 Spring
This tour will be my last tour, so please look forward to it.
This will be my last tour, so please look forward to it.
On March 30 and 31, Ina Fest 2024 will be held at the Q Hall of the Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall.
Ina Fest 2024 will be held at Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall Q on March 30 and 31.
Also on March 30 and 31
Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall
Carbon Neutral 2024 by Satosanoumi Movement
by Satosanzanoumi Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall on March 30 and 31.
Hello Project members
We are looking forward to seeing you at both Inafes and Satosanoumi.
We look forward to seeing you at both Inafes and Satoyama Umi.
And Angerme will be performing at "sdd" on March 9th.
This will be our second time to perform at sdd.
This will be the second time we've performed at sdd.
I'm looking forward to it this time too!
Please do your best!
Morning Musume 24 Angerme will perform on May 3
BEYOND will perform at Japan Jam 2024 on May 4!
Thank you very much.
Morning Musume 24 and Angerme have performed several times.
Diones... I'm glad to hear you're joining our ranks.
I'm very happy.
I was so surprised.
Congratulations!
I know it's a different date, but I wish I could have seen it!
I know the dates are different, but I'm sure all three teams will be on top of their game, so let's all enjoy the festival!
I'll be waiting for you!
I'll be waiting for you! Project is a channel where the members of Hello!
Project members every Wednesday, so be sure to subscribe to the channel!